What happening?!
To hell with you, Kaido!
New Onigashima
So you are behind this!
The, Kozuki’s parade of ghouls!
Orochi-sama...
already died once.
Fukurokuju!
Allow me to handle them...
Well, you would be, wouldn’t you? s
after all!
every last one of you!
Listen here! I’m going to...
have all of your heads!
We will do battle right here!
who it issyou face?!
Know your. place, filth!
of the Land of Wano!
am not the villain here!
what was coming to them!
merely’
y took back what was mine!
fail to understand...
and obey his word!
am'a man of power!
Flower Shuriken!
my oppressors —-this nation!
Th-That look in your eyes!
athat I’m wrong?! f, Os.
Don’t look at me...
cannot be wrong!
top look t like that!
tOP Ing at me like tna
Let us be off! Ge
Will you avenge your lord, then?
Fukurokuju!
you remained loyal to him ‘til the end...
of all of you!
you and were destined to fight!
do you not... Raizo!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
forge alread? map as
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
Gna your as you go!
We can t even tell left from right
in this tempest tossed era
a Even the values We ve honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you Il find your soul guiding the
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind G
and kick away the darkness!
and kick.
and k y th
ick away the darkness!
and you re doing this for yourself too, right?
AS Forse ahead, painting the world your own colors!
the colors
wor owe
is such a pain in the ass.
This ain’t doin’ any wonders for my health.
Stick it to ‘em, Kaido?
g live to tell the tale...
down below with your ability?
would’ve done it already.
can’t move them!
How’s about we tear ‘em apart?
Hey, here comes the big one!
got strong legs, hag!
you’re talking to, brat?!
High Seas Supremacy!
no dodging that!
sing
Get Outta here, guys!
Get guys!
there...
als gonna’get you dead!
but can still hear their voices...
Color me impressed.
Zoroer, you still breathing?
think so...
even for just a moment. Thanks.
Where’s Straw Hat?
Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
Made ya jump, Kaido!
Must be ‘cause it hurts!
Stick it to ‘em!
Damned
Kaido!
Three Worlds:
Ragnaraku!
Luffy:
of the trash, too!
Done!
Room:
Chambres!
It’s dark in here!
Can you do it, Roronoa?!
Ain’t like got a choice!
Crossing the Six Paths!
top! I’m j
p! I’m just a sword!
Mama, save me!
My children!
Punk Pistols!
What’s this, now?!
from them?! ay
by cutting me off from them?!
Takt!
wonjt be dongin by, thrown at me!
Oh, damn it!
Mama!
then that takes care of one of them!
Save me, right now!
Zeuuuus!
Mama!
What’s wrong, Mama?!
Scream for me!
Say goodbye to the old bag!
The sea...
Will take rest.
Buwhat are byou doinbu?!
Probmetheusbu!
Mam
on my wa—
That moron...
High Seas Supremacy!
no dodging that!
a here, guys!
shattered from taking that?!
Pathetic, Linlin!
Do gotta do everything for you?
Hey, Pirate Hunter!
Let Prometheus go!
Chambres!
Injection Shot!
that ability of yours...
Curtain! ><
Go away!
wn aaa mac aa!
Hey, Traf!
That fire thing’s...
on its way to save Big Mom!
Just let him go...
rather the plan fail...
one of us die.
Mama!
What’s going on, Mama?!
Big Mom and Kaido apart! ‘4
put your lives on the line!
Leave Big Mom to me!
Mama!
My savior!
Thank goodness, Mama!
What the hell is Zeus doing?!
He’s useless to me!
Mama!
our family anymore!
got something to ask you, Mama!
something to
want a girlfriend!
That’s a good idea!
A new child to replace Zeus...
It’s... Just like the last time!
but he’s still...
Maybe oughta...
smash those eyes In first?
Or maybe...
Mis brain?
Or his heart?
Traf.
I’m about to show this guy...
what I’m made of.
Zoroer?!
Sloppy fighting...
1S Only gonna wear us down.
It was just my time.
Then everything else...
Hey, Kaido!
That? in!
at’s our captain
wel Why don’tcha give...
Dashin’ my head ina try
my head try first?!
Blades Drawn! y
Nine-Sword Style...
Dead Man’s Game!
Damn!
This whelp...
Conqueror’s Haki too?!
What are you talking about?
You’re making no sense!
into that one attack!
Would’ve liked that...
You did enough.
This scar’s gonna be permanent.
generation.
Hey! Zoroer, run!
Shame...
and we can rule the world...
With you?
Who’d wanna join your crew?
Ya jerk.
the samural.
ite
onn
ick
Kick my ass?
I’d love to see you try!
That is, if you even can...
all bark, no bite!
yourself, now!
capable of defending you like invisible armor,
for use in offense.
if you take it one step further,
strengthens even more,
destroying it from the inside!
So don’t strain yourself!
that don’t into your fists.
Kong Gun!
Still not deep enough...
you hit me with your spiked club.
Conqueror’s Haki too, huh?
gonna help you?
You really think you can do that?
Only a handful...
can pull it off!
Not some dead man walking!
intosyour
into that one attack!
generation.
ONS You’re fighting a true monster!
a have it in you!
He’s nottev him...!
Zoro...
Traf...
Thanks for keepin’ me safe.
the both of ya!
Tell everybody for me...
Said that!